We have to work hard for our studio's survival.
為了生存也只能辛苦大家了
Let's wrap up this meeting.
那就先散會吧
I'll send everyone the script a little later.
晚點再把劇本發給大家
All right. I want to ask each of you to make sure you take care of your own preparation work.
再麻煩各位各自進行負責的前置工作囉
Thank you for your hard work.
辛苦了
Hey, Rosie Lin, come sit down for a minute.
哎 林香妳坐一下
I have something I want to talk to you about.
有事跟妳聊聊
Take a look.
你看
Hey, when your at work you should be working.
哎上班就上班
Why are you shooting & filming this?
妳在給我拍這個
That's crazy.
太過份了吧
How am I being crazy?
哦哪有
I don't have any work right now!
我又沒有工作
Hey
誒
Let me tell you something.
我跟你說
I still have the nude pics on my cell phone.
我手機裡面還有沒穿衣服版本的
Do you want to see it?
你要不要看
No…No…No
哎 好
Stop making a scene! Don't make a scene.
妳不要鬧 不要鬧
You're such a pervert!
真的很變態哎
Come on, it's not that bad.
還好吧
Well, even if someone else wanted to see it, they can't.
哎別人要看又沒有這些可以看
Oh!
哦
OK. Ok
好啦
I have something I want to talk to you about that is very important.
我有認真的事情要跟妳講
I have some works for you to do.
有工作給妳
Come here and check out this project.
來 看一下這個
Well, our new project is a little more complicated this time around.
這次啊 我們這個企劃比較複雜一點
And that you are also in charge of the cosplayer's roles for the project.
然後妳負責這個Coser的部分
Then you have to get me a set of sexy lingerie.
那要幫我準備一套性感的內衣哦
Ok, done, no problem.
好啊沒問題
Let me tell you. I 'm really good at picking out lingerie.
我跟你講這是我最擅長的
Well, in that case.
那這樣的話
Do you want to go shopping with me after work?
下班你要不要陪我去買
Huh? Why would I go shopping with you?
蛤 為什麼我要陪妳去買
Ah….Please!
嗯哼 拜託嘛
All right.
好
We'll talk after work.
下班再說
Yes, you are the best!
耶 你對我最好了
See you after work.
那下班見囉
So, it's a date.
這是我們的約會哦
You pinky promise!
打勾勾哦
OK. Ok
好啦
Love you.
愛你哦
I really can't stand you.
真的是受不了
Ugh, I can't stand you.
哦真受不了哎
Ugh. What are you doing?
哎幹嘛
Do you like the way my skirt looks?
我裙子好看嗎
It's too short.
太短了吧
Your ass is hanging out for everyone to see.
妳屁股都要被人看光了啦
It's not that bad. You are such an old fart!
還好吧你是老人喔
Okay, it's fine.
好吧 沒事
Forget about it.
當我沒說
So, we are here
那都到了
I'm going to wait for you out front.
我在門口這裡等妳吧
What? You're not coming in with me?
什麼你不跟我一起去嗎
No, I don't want to go in.
我不要
I'll just wait for you here.
我在這裡等妳就好了
Aww, come on, come on.
哦來啦來啦
Come on, lets go in together.
來嘛一起一起
Mmn…OK.
哦好吧
Don't worry.
不要擔心
Come on, let's go!
快點一起上來
Come.
來
Wow, look that!
哎你看這個
Look at that. It has really big boobs.
你看這個 它奶超大的
It Looks like they feel really nice to touch.
看起來很好摸哎
It looks so bouncy & fun.
看起來很彈哎
I really want to grab them.
好想抓看看
They really are very pretty.
真的很漂亮
Yes they are!
對啊
It's skin is better than mine.
皮膚比我還好哎
Sigh
欸
I've got the exact same one.
哎這個我有一模一樣的耶
Let me tell you something.
我跟你說
Come on let me tell you a little secret.
真的我跟你說
I use it every morning.
我每天早上的時候都會用一下
Huh?
蛤
So is that why you're always late in the morning.
所以妳早上遲到該不會都是
I'm not telling you.
不跟你說
That's so cool.
好酷喔
What is this?
這什麼
Sigh
欸
Take a look at this one. It goes up and down.
你看這個它會往上往下哎
Yep, it's looks pretty awesome.
對啊看起來很厲害
It looks really cool.
看起來好酷喔
So cool
太酷了
There's so much amazing stuff.
好多好神奇的東西哦
Wow. It looks like you're in paradise.
哇妳的天堂到了
Holy cow there is so many!
超多的
Look at this lingerie.
看一下
This one looks amazing.
這個看起來還不錯哎
Take a look.
你看一下
Can I try it on?
是可以這樣打開來試的嗎
I'm sorry but no, you can open it to take a closer look at it.
沒有試 是打開來看看
Oh!
哦
Wow, look
哎你看
This one is great.
好看吧
Yes, it looks good.
嗯 這件質感還不錯哎
Yep, I think it'll look really nice on me.
對啊 我穿起來應該會很好看
Let me look at another one.
我再看一下另外一件
This one kind of looks like a nurse's outfit.
有點護士的感覺
Yes they are!
對啊
Which one do you like?
要選哪一件
Can I get both of them?
還是我兩件都買
Sure why not!
好像可以耶
Then I'll buy it and wear it for you to look at.
那我買回去穿給你看
Sure.
好啊
Pay for it.
結帳
Let's go.
走吧
Senior classmate, does this lingerie look good on me?
學長好看嗎